Jevin vaghasiya

Full stack Developer

As a passionate and dedicated full stack developer, I have completed my internship and now thrive as a full-time professional in the field, I specialize in designing, developing, and deploying secure applications. I am ready to take on new challenges and learn new advancement technologies to make a meaningful impact in the world of development.

Contact



9925840336



jevinvaghasiya102@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/jevin-vaghasiya/



Ahmedabad, India

Skills

- Node JS
- Angular
- React JS
- Hapi JS
- Express JS
- JavaScript
- TypeScrpit

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

Certificate

 Responsive Web Design (freeCodeCamp)

Education

GSEB

2017
SSC
2019
Passed it with a 79.16%

GHSEB

2017
Hsc
2019
Passed it with a 68.46%

Silver Oak University
B.Tech
Current 7th sem CGPA is 9.41

Work Experience

Web Development

Mavisoft infotech

06/2022 - 07/2022

It was about one month educational internship provided by the company.

- Usage of HTML and CSS for making templates.
- Hand to hand experience with JavaScript for making templates more interactive.

Full Stack Developer - Intern

Techivies Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

09/2022 - 09/2023

In the span of my internship I learned all the core concepts of Angular, Node JS with Hapi JS and MongoDB from Udemy courses, Youtube, documentation and diff. articles.

Full Stack Developer

Techivies Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

10/2023 - Present

Learning and building real-life, impactful Systems by applying my evolving Full Stack Development skills.